PERSONAL DETAILS

Name

Bárbara Cassiram

Addross

Luján, Buenos Aires - Argentina

Phone number

+5491128450190

Email

cassiram15@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/barb ara-cassiram/

Website

https://cassiramb.vercel.app/

TECHNOLOGIES

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

React.js

Redux

Node.js

Express

PostgreSQL

Sequelize

GIT

Figma

Scrum

SKILLS

Teamwork

Active listening

Good communication skills

Problem solving

Creativity

Adaptability

Self-taught

LANGUAGES

English

B2

Bárbara Cassiram

Full Stack Developer oriented to Front End, with knowledge in JavaScript, React, Redux, HTML, CSS, Node.js, SQL. I seek to contribute with creativity and innovation in achieving the overall goals of the company, developing myself through continuous learning and teamwork, in order to acquire more experience and self-improvement.

PROJECTS

Full Stack Web Developer - Mi Scusi Books.

Oct 2022 - Nov 2022

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Design and develop a book e-commerce that included: login, registration, product filtering and sorting, payment gateway, PDF reading on the site, email notifications, reviews, chatbot, responsive design, among other features.
- Develop the app implementing React, Redux, CSS, MUI, Ant Design for the front end. Back end developed in Node with Express implementing JavaScript. Database in MongoDB. Implementation of Nodemailer, GoogleCloud, Cloudinary, DialogFlow, Paypal.

Deploy: https://mi-scusi-books.vercel.app/ - Repository: https://github.com/cassirambd/Mi-Scusi-Books

Full Stack Web Developer - Dogs App.

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Design and development of a dog breeds app that included: landing page, filters and sorting, creation form, responsive design, among other features.
- Develop the app implementing React, Redux, pure CSS for the front end. Back end developed in Node with Express implementing JavaScript. Database in PostgreSQL and Sequelize.

Deploy: https://pi-dogs-byk.vercel.app/ - Repository: https://github.com/cassirambd/PI-DOGS

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Teaching Assistant

Sep 2022 - Nov 2022

Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina

- Coordinate a group of students to achieve integration to the study group.
- Guide students in the first steps of the course.
- Assist to solve exercises and promote group collaboration (Pair Programming).

Multifunction Operator

Jul 2021 - Jan 2022

Johnson & Johnson Vision Care, Buenos Aires, Argentina

- · Plan the picking and assembly of orders.
- Verify the good condition and expiration date of the product.
- · Packing, labeling, storing and general tasks.

Production Operator

Jan 2021 - Jun 2021

Don Quique Alfajores, Buenos Aires, Argentina

- Perform assembly of merchandise on production lines.
- Comply with quality controls, tests and follow safety methods.
- Pack and store merchandise.

PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Developer. Henry Bootcamp. +700 theoretical-practical course hours. 2022. **Clinical Laboratory Technician.** U.E.P. Colegio Cristo Rey. 2011 - 2017.

COMPLEMENTARY EDUCATION

Fundamentals of Programming. Udemy. 2022

Cabin Crew. Escuela Aeronavegantes. 2020 - 2021.

Extractionist and Clinical Laboratory Management. CFP Mariano Moreno. 2018 - 2019